module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'My cousin broke up Ashton Kutcher and Demi Moore.', 
    a: 'TayTae',
    b: 'Brady',
    c: 'Tyler Hollywood',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I own a travel company called Triplapser', 
    a: 'Dante',
    b: 'BDF',
    c: 'Tyler N',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'My first words ever were "ice ice baby."', 
    a: 'Kevin',
    b: 'Jake',
    c: 'Josh P',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'ve never gotten a speeding ticket....ever.', 
    a: 'JoCo',
    b: 'Troy',
    c: 'Billy',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I once went tornado chasing to impress a lady.', 
    a: 'JoCo',
    b: 'Joe',
    c: 'Glynn',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I was president of the latin honor society in high school.', 
    a: 'Adam',
    b: 'Haley',
    c: 'Elizabeth',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I was in the Baywatch movie with The Rock.', 
    a: 'West',
    b: 'JLowe',
    c: 'John',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I married my friend who was a flight attendant so I could fly for free.', 
    a: 'James',
    b: 'Brandon T',
    c: 'Geoff',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I used to be a RateMyProfessor.com moderator who took bribes.', 
    a: 'Billy',
    b: 'Aaron',
    c: 'Kevin',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I never graduated speech class.', 
    a: 'Devon',
    b: 'RA',
    c: 'Shannon',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];
